Guide to the Robert Flaherty Film Seminar Archive 1949 - 2011 MSS.326
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Flaherty Film Seminars
  - Subseries A: Audio Recordings
    - 23nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 16, September 1, 1977; ID: 326.0288 (Box 6, Media ID: 326.0288)
      Original Number: 1977-16
      Margie Short, Karen Kramer, Helen Whitney
    - 23nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 17, September 2, 1977; ID: 326.0289 (Box 6, Media ID: 326.0289, Box Shared Fales 134, Cd 326.0289_pt.1, Cd 326.0289_pt.2)
      Original Number: 1977-17
      Barbara Kopple, Hart Perry, Warren Bass, Jan Kravitz, Marnie Kirchheimer
    - 23nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 18, September 2,1977; ID: 326.0290 (Box 6, Media ID: 326.0290)
      Original Number: 1977-18
      Warner Bass, Jan Kravitz, Marnie Kirchheimer, Linda [Feferam]
    - 23nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 19, September 2, 1977; ID: 326.0291 (Box 6, Media ID: 326.0291)
      Original Number: 1977-19
      Linda Feferman, Alain Tanner
    - 23nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 20, September 3, 1977; ID: 326.0292 (Box 6, Media ID: 326.0292)
      Original Number: 1977-20
      Alain Tanner, Parry Miller Adato
    - 23nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 21, 1977; ID: 326.0293 (Box 6, Media ID: 326.0293)
      Original Number: 1977-21
      Last Saturday morning discussion
    - 24th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 1, 1978; ID: 326.0294 (Box 6, Media ID: 326.0294)
      Original Number: 1978-01
      Jay Ruby, George Stoney, Jean Rouch
    - 24th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 2, 1978; ID: 326.0295 (Box 6, Media ID: 326.0295)
      Original Number: 1978-02
      B Van Dyke, Roy Campanella Jr
    - 24th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 3, 1978; ID: 326.0296 (Box 6, Media ID: 326.0296)
      Original Number: 1978-03
      George Stoney, Trudy Bagdon, William Van Dyke, Jay Leyda
    - 24th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 4, 1978; ID: 326.0297 (Box 7, Media ID: 326.0297)
      Original Number: 1978-04
      Jean Ronsch
    - 24th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 5, 1978; ID: 326.0298 (Box 7, Media ID: 326.0298)
      Original Number: 1978-05
      Jean Rouch
    - 24th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 6, 1978; ID: 326.0299 (Box 7, Media ID: 326.0299)
      Original Number: 1978-06
      Mitchell Block - "Speeding" Ben Levin
    - 24th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 7, August 29, 1978; ID: 326.0300 (Box 7, Media ID: 326.0300)
      Original Number: 1978-07
      Jim [Pozz], Mitchell block & Murray, Vam Dyke, Ben Levin, Jill Godmilow - "Popovich Bros"
    - 24th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 9, 1978; ID: 326.0301 (Box 7, Media ID: 326.0301)
      Original Number: 1978-08
      Maxi Cohen, Joel Gold, Jean Pouch, Jay Ruby
    - 24th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 10, August 31, 1978; ID: 326.0302 (Box 7, Media ID: 326.0302)
      Original Number: 1978-09
      Jay leyda Jay Ruby
      Steve Mack Jay Ruby
    - 24th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 11, August 30, 1978; ID: 326.0303 (Box 7, Media ID: 326.0303)
      Original Number: 1978-10
      Jill Godmilow - "Popovich Rios"
    - 24th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 12, September 30, 1978; ID: 326.0304 (Box 7, Media ID: 326.0304)
      Original Number: 1978-11
      Jay Rudy
    - 24th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 13, 1978; ID: 326.0305 (Box 7, Media ID: 326.0305)
      Original Number: 1978-12
      [Jorben] Schioler, John Rouch
    - 24th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 14, 1978; ID: 326.0306 (Box 7, Media ID: 326.0306)
    - 24th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 15, September 1, 1978; ID: 326.0307 (Box 7, Media ID: 326.0307)
      Original Number: 1978-14
      Jean Rouch, "Peter Murray", Lorraine Gray, Jay Ruby
    - 24th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 16, 1978; ID: 326.0308 (Box 7, Media ID: 326.0308)
      Original Number: 1978-15
      Robin Smith - "He's Only Missing", Charles Cutler - [Tras Osmonty]
    - 24th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 17, September 1, 1978; ID: 326.0309 (Box 7, Media ID: 326.0309)
      Original Number: 1978-16
      Charles Cutler - [Tras As Montes]
    - 24th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 18, 1978; ID: 326.0310 (Box 7, Media ID: 326.0310)
      Original Number: 1978-17
      Lorraine Gray Evaluation
    - 24th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 19, 1978; ID: 326.0311 (Box 7, Media ID: 326.0311)
      Original Number: 1978-18
      Evaluation
    - 25th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 1, August 18, 1979; ID: 326.0312 (Box 8, Media ID: 326.0312)
      Original Number: 1979-01
      Marie Grieco, announcements by Barbara Van Dyke,
      The New Klan, Eleanor Bingham, Leslie Shatz, moderated by Bill Sloan
    - 25th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 2, August 18, 1979; ID: 326.0313 (Box 8, Media ID: 326.0313)
      Original Number: 1979-02
      The New Klan, Eleanor Bingham, Leslie Shatz.
      Erik Barnouw comments before Nancok, Opening remarks to The Land by Andries Deinum, My Survival as an Aboriginal M. Ansara
    - 25th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 3, August 19, 1979; ID: 326.0314 (Box 8, Media ID: 326.0314)
      Original Number: 1979-03
      Richard Rogers - "Cost of Living", Jay Ruby -moderator,
      Marceloina Loridan, Doris Ivans, Andries Deinum
    - 25th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 4, August 19, 1979; ID: 326.0315 (Box 8, Media ID: 326.0315)
      Original Number: 1979-04
      Martha [Musara] - "My Survival as an Aboriginal",
      Helen Van Dongan, comments to Louisanna Story,
      Bill Sloan [IraWoll], Best boy intro,
      J Agee, Ross Spear, Marie Grieco
    - 25th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 6, August 20, 1979; ID: 326.0316 (Box 8, Media ID: 326.0316)
      Original Number: 1979-06
      Joaquin Cortes, Barbara Margulis, Bill Sloan,
      Ira Woll, Best Boy, Esme Dick (mod),
      Ira Woll,
      Aug 21, George Stoney, Man of Aran
    - 25th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 7, August 21, 1979; ID: 326.0317 (Box 8, Media ID: 326.0317)
      Original Number: 1979-07
      George Stoney, Bill Sloan, Man of Aran, also Joris Ivens,
      Barry Braverman, Bill Sloan,
      Penny Bernstein, Bill Sloan, Paul Jacobs & nukegang
    - 25th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 8, August 21, 1979; ID: 326.0318 (Box 8, Media ID: 326.0318)
      Original Number: 1979-08
      Michael Blackwell, Austin [Lamont], George Segal.
      Aug 22: Charles Burnett, John Hanhardt, The Sheep Killers
    - 25th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 9, August 22, 1979; ID: 326.0319 (Box 8, Media ID: 326.0319)
      Original Number: 1979-09
      Outdoors, Charles Burnett, John Hanhardt, The Sheep Killers
    - 25th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 10, August 22, 1979; ID: 326.0320 (Box 8, Media ID: 326.0320)
      Original Number: 1979-10
      Penny Bernstein, Bill Sloan, Paul Jacobs & the Nuclear Gang, Jay Ruby - "Moana"
    - 25th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 13, August 23, 1979; ID: 326.0321 (Box 8, Media ID: 326.0321)
      Original Number: 1979-13
      Jonas Mekas, Marie Grieco - "To Jerome"
    - 25th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 14, August 23, 1979; ID: 326.0322 (Box 8, Media ID: 326.0322)
      Original Number: 1979-14
      Jonas Mekos, Marie Grieco, "To Jerome", Margaret Murphy, Barbara Van Dyke, "Noels", "Jewish Anarchist", Joel Suchar, Erica, Bill Sloan
    - 25th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 15, August 24, 1979; ID: 326.0323 (Box 8, Media ID: 326.0323)
      Original Number: 1979-15
      Joel Suchar, Erica, Bill Sloan, "Jewish Anarchist",
      George Stoney, John Clayton, "The Shepard of the Night Flock"
    - 25th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 16, August 25, 1979; ID: 326.0324 (Box 8, Media ID: 326.0324)
      Original Number: 1979-16
      Tony de Nonno, Jay Ruby,
      "Final Comments", Marie Grieco, Jay Ruby, Bill Sloan, Barbara Van Dyke
    - 25th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 17, August 25, 1979; ID: 326.0325 (Box 8, Media ID: 326.0325)
      Original Number: 1979-17
      "End Comments"
    - 26th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 1, August 16, 1980; ID: 326.0326 (Box 8, Media ID: 326.0326)
      Original Number: 1980-01
      Tape blank?
    - 26th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 2, August 17, 1980; ID: 326.0327 (Box 8, Media ID: 326.0327)
      Original Number: 1980-02
      Nunez Gal Young'un,
      Anne Schaetzer - "Breaking & Entering"
    - 26th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 3, August 17, 1980; ID: 326.0328 (Box 8, Media ID: 326.0328)
      Original Number: 1980-03
      Ann Schaetzel
    - 26th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 4, 1980; ID: 326.0329 (Box 8, Media ID: 326.0329)
      Original Number: 1980-04
      Tape maybe blank?
    - 26th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 6, August 17, 1980; ID: 326.0330 (Box 8, Media ID: 326.0330)
      Original Number: 1980-06
      "Trials of Alger Hiss" - John Lowenthal
    - 26th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 7, August 18, 1980; ID: 326.0331 (Box 8, Media ID: 326.0331)
      Original Number: 1980-07
      Discussion of N'ai: Filmmaker not present but [unknown] spoke on John Marshall's behalf,
      Anne [...]'s Rape film
    - 26th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 8, August 18, 1980; ID: 326.0332 (Box 8, Media ID: 326.0332)
      Original Number: 1980-08
      Rape Film, "A Scream From Silence" - Anne Clair Poirer
    - 26th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 9, August 18, 1980; ID: 326.0333 (Box 8, Media ID: 326.0333)
      Original Number: 1980-09
      Recordist: C. Mercier
    - 26th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 10, 1980; ID: 326.0334 (Box 8, Media ID: 326.0334)
      Original Number: 1980-10
      Abramowicz & Hoffenberg - "Comme si c'etait Hier",
      "Temp Morts" - John Katz
    - 26th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 11, August 18, 1980; ID: 326.0335 (Box 8, Media ID: 326.0335)
      Original Number: 1980-11
      "Temps Mort", Doris Chase, Warren Bass
    - 26th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 12, August 19, 1980; ID: 326.0336 (Box 8, Media ID: 326.0336)
      Original Number: 1980-12
      "Legacy" - Karen Arthur, "The War at Home" - Barry Brown
    - 26th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 13, August 19, 1980; ID: 326.0337 (Box 8, Media ID: 326.0337)
      Original Number: 1980-13
      "The War at Home", "[Solzhenitsyn]'s Children"
    - 26th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 14, August 20, 1980; ID: 326.0338 (Box 8, Media ID: 326.0338)
      Original Number: 1980-14
      End of Rubbo - "Solzhenitsyn's Children", Bob Young, [Cortile Cachio Alaubnista]!
    - 26th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 15, August 21, 1980; ID: 326.0339 (Box 8, Media ID: 326.0339)
      Original Number: 1980-15
      Alfred Guzzetti - "Scenes from Childhood", "Mobile Unit" - Derek May
    - 26th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 16, August 21, 1980; ID: 326.0340 (Box 8, Media ID: 326.0340)
      Original Number: 1980-16
      "Poto & Gagenga": discussed by John Katz, "Robeson": discussed by Saul Jurrell
    - 26th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 17, August 21, 1980; ID: 326.0341 (Box 8, Media ID: 326.0341)
      Original Number: 1980-17
      "Dr. Bethune": discussed by Gerald Tannebaum, Caroline Morris
    - 26th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 18, August 22, 1980; ID: 326.0342 (Box 8, Media ID: 326.0342)
      Original Number: 1980-18
      Duke Ellington: discussed by Gary Keys, Heartlands, Sex Pistols
    - 26th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 19, August 22, 1980; ID: 326.0343 (Box 8, Media ID: 326.0343)
      Original Number: 1980-19
      D.O.A.: discussed by Val Kuklowsky
    - 26th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 20, August 23, 1980; ID: 326.0344 (Box 8, Media ID: 326.0344)
      Original Number: 1980-20
      Suicide - No such thing as no chance Depression - Thirties America Lost & Found Tom Johnson
    - 26th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 21, August 23, 1980; ID: 326.0345 (Box 8, Media ID: 326.0345)
      Original Number: 1980-21
      Closing Discussion
    - 26th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 22, August 22, 1980; ID: 326.0346 (Box 8, Media ID: 326.0346)
      Original Number: 1980-22
    - 27th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 1, August 17, 1981; ID: 326.0347 (Box 8, Media ID: 326.0347)
      Original Number: 1981-01
      "Mad to Mozart", "Street Music", Nick Doob, Nadine Covert, Stan Lawder
    - 27th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 2, August 17, 1981; ID: 326.0348 (Box 8, Media ID: 326.0348)
      Original Number: 1981-02
      "A [Vady Namas] Baby, Carol Battoric, Brie Sloan, Stan Landen
    - 27th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 3, August 18, 1981; ID: 326.0349 (Box 8, Media ID: 326.0349)
      Original Number: 1981-03
      "Diaries", Ed Pincus, Austin [Lamons]
    - 27th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 4, August 18, 1981; ID: 326.0350 (Box 8, Media ID: 326.0350)
      Original Number: 1981-04
      "Diaries", Ed Pincus, Austin Lamont
    - 27th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 5, August 18, 1981; ID: 326.0351 (Box 8, Media ID: 326.0351)
      Original Number: 1981-05
      "Wilmer 8", Julie Tampson, Barbara Van Dyke
    - 27th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 6, August 18, 1981; ID: 326.0352 (Box 8, Media ID: 326.0352)
      Original Number: 1981-06
      "Conversations with Willard Van Dyke", [Amalie Rothcain]
    - 27th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 7, August 19, 1981; ID: 326.0353 (Box 8, Media ID: 326.0353)
      Original Number: 1981-07
      "We Are One People", Gabor Kalma
    - 27th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 8, August 19, 1981; ID: 326.0354 (Box 8, Media ID: 326.0354)
      Original Number: 1981-08
      "Herzog", Les Blank, Mitch Block
    - 27th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 9, August 19, 1981; ID: 326.0355 (Box 8, Media ID: 326.0355)
      Original Number: 1981-09
      "Stations of Elevators", Manyy Kitchcimer, Louis Hock
    - 27th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 10, August 20, 1981; ID: 326.0356 (Box 8, Media ID: 326.0356)
      Original Number: 1981-10
      "Day After Trinity", [Johu Else] filmmaker, Hugh Bradner
    - 27th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 11, August 20, 1981; ID: 326.0357 (Box 8, Media ID: 326.0357)
      Original Number: 1981-11
      "Day After Trinity", [Joshua Else]
    - 27th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 12, August 20, 1981; ID: 326.0358 (Box 8, Media ID: 326.0358)
      Original Number: 1981-12
      David [Bruton], Stan [Lander]
    - 27th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 13, August 20, 1981; ID: 326.0359 (Box 8, Media ID: 326.0359)
      Original Number: 1981-13
      David [Britta] Films, Stan [Lauder]
    - 27th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 14, August 21, 1981; ID: 326.0360 (Box 8, Media ID: 326.0360)
      Original Number: 1981-14
      "Why Can't It Be Someone Else", [Bin Conterie], John [Korty]
    - 27th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 15, August 21, 1981; ID: 326.0361 (Box 8, Media ID: 326.0361)
      Original Number: 1981-15
      "Why Can't it Be Someone Else", [Bin Contevier], John [Korny]
    - 27th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 16, August 21, 1981; ID: 326.0362 (Box 8, Media ID: 326.0362)
      Original Number: 1981-16
      "Carny", David [Nugaut]-Walter Thomas, "8 to Midnight", Ernie Rose, Austin Laums
    - 27th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 17, August 22, 1981; ID: 326.0363 (Box 8, Media ID: 326.0363)
      Original Number: 1981-17
      "The Shepards of [Bernaray], Allan Moore, Alan Rosenthal
    - 27th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 18, August 22, 1981; ID: 326.0364 (Box 8, Media ID: 326.0364)
      Original Number: 1981-18
      Wrap Up
    - 28th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 1, August 14, 1982; ID: 326.0365 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0365)
      Original Format: audio tape
      Original Number: 1982-01
      "Wasn't That a Time?", George Stoney, Ronnie Gilbert, Jim Brown, Ginger Turek, moderated by Erik Barnouw, The Weavers
    - 28th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 2, August 15, 1982; ID: 326.0366 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0366)
      Original Number: 1982-02
      "Smothering Dreams", Dan Reeves, moderated by Erik Barnouw
    - 28th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 3, August 15, 1982; ID: 326.0367 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0367)
      Original Number: 1982-03
      "All My Babies", George Stoney, Erik Barnouw
    - 28th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 4, August 15, 1982; ID: 326.0368 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0368)
      Original Number: 1982-04
      "6 O'clock and All's Well", Robert Spencer, Erik Barnouw-moderator
    - 28th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 5, August 15, 1982; ID: 326.0369 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0369)
      Original Number: 1982-05
      "She & He", Schiko Hidari, Andrea [Gladstone]- translator, Erik Barnow- moderator
    - 28th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 6, August 16, 1982; ID: 326.0370 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0370)
      Original Number: 1982-06
      "Shepard of teh Night Flock", George Stoney, Jim Brown, Erik Barnow- moderator
    - 28th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 7, August 16, 1982; ID: 326.0371 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0371)
      Original Number: 1982-07
      George Stoney, videotapes from Minnesota
    - 28th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 8, August 16, 1982; ID: 326.0372 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0372)
      Original Number: 1982-08
      "Clockwork", Eric [Biebeut], Erik Barnouw- moderator
    - 28th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 9, August 16, 1982; ID: 326.0373 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0373)
      Original Number: 1982-09
      "Under the Flag of the Rising Sun", Sachiko Hidari - actress, Audrey Gladstone - interpreter, Erik Barnouw - moderator
    - 28th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 10, August 16, 1982; ID: 326.0374 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0374)
      Original Number: 1982-10
      [Elutino Baile], Regge Life, Erik Barnouw, "My God hat have We Done", Dutch filmmakers
    - 28th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 11, August 16, 1982; ID: 326.0375 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0375)
      Original Number: 1982-11
      "A Ballet Class", Jack [Churchill], ["Meda Mayam"], Dan Reaves, "Kids & Nuclear War"
    - 28th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 12, August 17, 1982; ID: 326.0376 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0376)
      Original Number: 1982-12
      "Against Wind & Sea", Paul [Neshamkin] - producer, Erik Barnouw, "An Acquired Taste", Ralph Arlyck, "Working Through Changes", Pat Cooper
    - 28th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 13, August 17, 1982; ID: 326.0377 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0377)
      Original Number: 1982-13
      Atomic Cafe, Project Puffin, [Susan Oristaelio], Carol Lee Taylor, "Not A Love Story", Kathleen Shannon - executive producer
    - 28th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 14, August 18, 1982; ID: 326.0378 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0378)
      Original Number: 1982-14
      "Not A Love Story", "The Far Road", Sachiko Hidari
    - 28th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 15, August 19, 1982; ID: 326.0379 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0379)
      Original Number: 1982-15
      "The Far Road", Maya Angelou, David Grubin, "Still Life", "Butter Button", Juan Mandubaum- producer, "Fable Safe", Erik Barnouw
    - 28th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 16, August 19, 1982; ID: 326.0380 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0380)
      Original Number: 1982-16
      "Let Poland Be Poland", Charles [Beuron]
    - 28th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 17, August 20, 1982; ID: 326.0381 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0381)
      Original Number: 1982-17
      "Bride of the Andes", Sachio Hidari, "Miles of Smiles", "Years of Struggle"
    - 28th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 18, August 20, 1982; ID: 326.0382 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0382)
      Original Number: 1982-18
      "Miles of Smiles", "Bood & Sand", Peter Kinoy, "Insect W0man"
    - 28th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 19, August 20, 1982; ID: 326.0383 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0383)
      Original Number: 1982-19
      "Insect Woman", "Echoes & Silences", Perry Miller [Adajo]
    - 28th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 20, August 21, 1982; ID: 326.0384 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0384)
      Original Number: 1982-20
      Final Discussion
    - 28th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 21, August 21, 1982; ID: 326.0385 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0385)
      Original Number: 1982-21
    - 29th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 1, August 14, 1983; ID: 326.0386 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0386)
      Original Number: 1983-01
      Opening Remarks, Tidlat
    - 29th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 2, 1983; ID: 326.0387 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0387)
      Original Number: 1983-02
      J. Honig, Jeff [Kleines], Joel McDoit
    - 29th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 3, 1983; ID: 326.0388 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0388)
      Original Number: 1983-03
      Jeff & Bill Farley
    - 29th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 4, 1983; ID: 326.0389 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0389)
      Original Number: 1983-04
      Bill Farley, Jill
    - 29th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 6, August 16, 1983; ID: 326.0390 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0390)
      Original Number: 1983-06
      [Michelle Citeon]
    - 29th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 7, 1983; ID: 326.0391 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0391)
      Original Number: 1983-07
      Trinh
    - 29th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 8, 1983; ID: 326.0392 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0392)
      Original Number: 1983-08
      Trinh, Lee Sokol, [Kidlat]
    - 29th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 9, 1983; ID: 326.0393 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0393)
      Original Number: 1983-09
      Kidlak [Tahimik]
    - 29th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 10, 1983; ID: 326.0394 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0394)
      Original Number: 1983-10
      Skip blumberg
    - 29th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 11, 1983; ID: 326.0395 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0395)
      Original Number: 1983-11
      Marie Grieco, Bill Viola, Tribute to Bill alexander ?
    - 29th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 12, 1983; ID: 326.0396 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0396)
      Original Number: 1983-12
      Bill Viola
    - 29th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 13, 1983; ID: 326.0397 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0397)
      Original Number: 1983-13
      L Hurwitz
    - 29th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 14, 1983; ID: 326.0398 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0398)
      Original Number: 1983-14
      Julia Reichert
    - 29th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 15, August 18, 1983; ID: 326.0399 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0399)
      Original Number: 1983-15
    - 29th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 16, 1983; ID: 326.0400 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0400)
      Original Number: 1983-16
    - 29th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 17, August 19, 1983; ID: 326.0401 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0401)
      Original Number: 1983-17
      Paper Tiger, Dee Dee Malleck
    - 29th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 18, 1983; ID: 326.0402 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0402)
      Original Number: 1983-18
    - 29th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 19, August 20, 1983; ID: 326.0403 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0403)
      Original Number: 1983-19
      Wrap-up Discussion
    - 30th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 2, August 11, 1984; ID: 326.0404 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0404)
      Original Number: 1984-02
      Saturday Morning
    - 30th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 3, August 11, 1984; ID: 326.0405 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0405)
      Original Number: 1984-03
      Saturday Afternoon
    - 30th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 4, August 11, 1984; ID: 326.0406 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0406)
      Original Number: 1984-04
      Saturday Afternoon - Evening
    - 30th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 5, August 12, 1984; ID: 326.0407 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0407)
      Original Number: 1984-05
      Saturday Evening 8/11/84, Sunday Morning 8/12/84
    - 30th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 6, August 12, 1984; ID: 326.0408 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0408)
      Original Number: 1984-06
      [VeVe] Clark
    - 30th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 7, August 12, 1984; ID: 326.0409 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0409)
      Original Number: 1984-07
      Bruce Connor
    - 30th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 9, 1984; ID: 326.0410 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0410)
      Original Number: 1984-09
      Monk
    - 31st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 1, August 10, 1985; ID: 326.0411 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0411)
      Original Number: 1985-01
      "Democracy On Trial", Paul Cowan
    - 31st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 2, August 11, 1985; ID: 326.0412 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0412)
      Original Number: 1985-02
      Kenneth Harrison
    - 31st Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 3, August 11, 1985; ID: 326.0413 (Box 9, Media ID: 326.0413)